亲爱的你气色不太好
Oh, honey, you don't lookso good.
-吃完早餐后留在家里吧  -真的?
-You should stayhome from brunch. -Are you sure?
-我真的想去  -留下来休息吧
-I really want togo. -You stay and rest.
我们回来后你就可看到奶奶
You cansee Grandma whenwe get back.
谢谢你录影带店的垃圾箱
Thank you, Videobarn dumpster.
要干我吗宝贝?
Wanna fuck me, baby?
-要  -你要干我吗?
-Oh, yes. -Yeah.You wanna fuck me?
艾瑞克你知道我的剪刀  还在你爸那里吗?
Hey, Erik. Do youknow ifyour dad still has my clippers?
我不知道威廉斯先生
I have no idea, Mr. Williams.
好吧  继续回去办你的事
All right. Go back to what you were doing.
你要干我吗  宝贝?
You wanna fuck me, baby?
要
Yeah.
-干我吧宝贝  -当然
-Yeah. Fuck me, baby. -Yes, please.
干我
Oh, do me, baby.
甜心
Honey.
那样就对了
Yeah, just like that.
对了!  好爽
Oh, yeah! so good, so good, baby.
好爽!
Oh, yeah!
我说过我付钱
I told you I waspaying.
你没带折价券有什么关系?
so what's the differenceif you forgot the coupon?
甜心  她只是不想浪费钱
Honey, she doesn't like to waste money.
梳理台上有一张买一送一的折价券
There'sno way I'm letting you pay full price
我当然不能让你多付钱
when there's a two-for-one coupon sitting on the counter.
-我马上出来  -我也一起去我要小便
-I'll beright out. -I'mcoming, too. Now I gotta pee.
我去看看艾瑞克
I'll check on Erik.
-爽啊  -真爽
-Oh, yeah. -Oh. Oh, that's good.
-你喜欢吗?  我也喜欢  -好爽!
-You like that? Ilike that, too. -Oh, yeah!
-来吧  -好  妈
-Here wego. -Okay, Mom.
-再用力一点  -再用力?  好
-Harder. -Harder?Okay.
好爽!
Oh, yeah! so good.
-像这样? -对  那里
-Like this? -Yeah, rightthere, babe.
-这样? -对
-Like this? Likethis? -Yeah.
像那样干我
Baby, dome justlike that.
好  很好
Okay, attagirl.
-从后面? -对  用力点!
-From behind? -Oh, yeah,baby! Harder!
-好  -好
-Okay. -All right.
-你要射出来了吗? -对
-You wanna cum for me, baby? -Oh, yeah.
-是吗?射吧  -我快出来了对
-Yeah? Cum for me, baby.-I'm so close. I will.
快了
We're almost there.
-你要射了吗?  -要射了
-You'regonna cumfor me?-I'm about to. I'm about to.
来
That's it, baby.
奶奶
Grandma.Grandma.
Grandma.
我奶奶就是那天去世的
And that's the day my grandmother died.
我的生活差不多就是这样
And it'spretty much thestory of my life.
不过让我从头讲起
But letme backthings up a little bit.
那就是我在派对中并不起眼
That's me. Not exactly the life of the party.
那是我朋友  麦克库斯曼
That's my buddy,Mike Coozeman.
大家都叫他库斯  因为他只喜欢把妹子
Everybody calls him Coozecause that's all he's ever interested in.
库斯自称风流倜傥以为自己把妹子很行
Cooze isa self-proclaimed ladies' man and a legend in his own mind.
但有时他的方法
sometimes his methods are...
让人不敢苟同
questionable.
好厉害
Very smooth.
拜托  那算是前戏
Oh, please. I consider that foreplay.
-莱恩呢? -不知道
-Where'sRyan? -Idon't know.
刚刚才看到他在跟史黛西和雪莉跳舞
Last time I saw him, he was dancing with stacey and shelly.
那是我最好的朋友莱恩葛林
That's my best friend, Ryan Grimm.
我不知道他怎么办到的
I don'tknow howhe doesit.
我就说够让你们两个躺
see, I told you there wasenough for both of you.
他二年级时搬到附近来
He movedhere insecond grade.
你相信吗那时他还需要我教呢
Believeit or not, back then, I was the one showing him the ropes.
现在他是足球队的四分卫
Now he'sthe quarterbackof the football team,
也是全校最酷的男生
and thecoolest guy in school.
嘿  我拿了伏特加和葱汁汽水给你
Hey, I brought you a vodka and ginger ale
这样你才不会闹肚子
so it won't upsetyour stomach.
谢了
Oh, thanks.
那是我女朋友崔西
That's my girlfriend, Tracy.
我们在高一生物课上认识的
We met in Biology, junioryear.
现在对青蛙切下第一刀
Now makethe first incision into your frogs.
往腹部切下去  顺着骨盆方向直到胸
Cut along the ventral side, from the pelvic to the pectoral girdle.
噢!
Oh!
我不知道她喜欢我哪一点
I don'tknow whatshe sawin me,
不过当我鼓足勇气约她出去时她同意了
but whenI finally got upthe nerve to ask her out, she said yes.
没关系
No, it'sokay.
不知道为什么  她一直跟我在一起
And forsome reason, shekept going out with me.
好像她完全了解我
It's like she totally gets me.
我尽量试着去了解她
And I try my bestto gether.
来  试试低的那个很容易
Come on.Take thelow one. It's easy.
来吧
screw it.
噢!
Oh!
你没事吧?
Are youall right?
不知道有没有人摔破屁股的?
I don'tknow. Isit possible to break your ass?
好  我保证不再叫你骑马了
Okay, Ipromise I'll never make you ride a horse again.
她好像很完美  对吧?  只有一个问题
Looks like she'sperfect,right? There's just one problem.
崔西还不想嘿咻  所以我也还是处男
Tracy'snot readyto havesex yet, so that makes me a virgin.
身为学校中仅有的处男之一已经够惨了
Now, being one ofthe only virgins in school is bad enough,
但还有更惨的呢
but it'seven worse for me.
对
Yup.
我是史提夫家的人
I'm a Stifler.
我的表哥表弟就是名扬四海的史提夫孩子
My cousins are the legendary Stifler boys.
史帝夫他的弟弟麦特
steve, his brother, Matt,
还有我们的另一个表哥杜埃特
and ourother cousin, Dwight.
因为我是这个家族的人  因此有一份责任
You see,with mylast name comes responsibility,
绝不能丢人现眼
a reputation thatI'm supposed to live up to.
不过我已经多次让家人失望
Unfortunately, I've let down the family name on more than one occasion.
搞屁啊艾瑞克?
What's your problem, Erik?
如果是你表哥  一定会帮我偷啤酒
Your cousin would've helped me steal this beer.
如果你真的是史提夫家的人
Dude, areal Stifler
一定会去干那头山羊
would have totally fuckedthat goat.
如果你真的是史提夫家的人你早就跟崔西上床了
lf you were really a Stifler, you would have nailed Tracy by now.
史提夫
Stifler.
我的姓我的家族渊源  我的诅咒
My name,my legacy, my curse.
我真不敢相信你居然因为自慰而让奶奶一命呜呼
I can'tbelieve you killed your grandmother from Jerking off.
验尸报告没有明确说明
The coroner's findings were inconclusive.
你干嘛还对着那  垃圾箱捡来的A片打枪?
Why areyou stillwhacking it to that dumpster porn?
对啊  你怎么不像正常人一样上网?
Yeah, why don't you Justgo on the lnternet like a normal person?
因为那天你一整晚在看
Well, because mymom puton that CyberNanny
德国恋物癖色情片所以我妈安装了网路分级装置
after you spent the entire night looking up German fetish porn.
你真可悲
Man, youare pathetic.
你知道我要怪谁?崔西
You knowwho I blame forthis? Tracy.
啊?  为什么?
What? Why?
因为如果她肯让你爽一下
Because,if she would Just give up a little ass,
那你就不会把你亲戚射死了
then maybe you wouldn't be killing your relatives with your money shot.
艾瑞克你不能以处男之身毕业
Erik, you cannotgraduatea virgin.
你还是史提夫家族的人呢
For Christ's sake, you're a Stifler.
甜心  你的数学课如何?
Hey, sweetie. Howwas your math class?
还好  你的英文课呢?
It was all right.How wasEnglish?
其实挺有意思的
Pretty interesting, actually.
你知道我常告诉你的那个孩子吗?
You knowthat kidthat Ialways tell you about?
-他一直用铅笔在...  -好
-He wasdoing that pencilthing all... -That's cool.
-你没事吧?  -没事
-Are Youokay? -Yeah, I'mfine.
艾瑞克我们交往两年了
Erik, we've beendating for two years.
你不高兴我看得出来
I know when something's bothering you.
没事
Nothing's wrong.
我不知道你为什么觉得  自己能看透我
I don'tknow whyyou think you have this psychic ability to read me.
因为我就是能  到底怎么了?
BecauseI do. What is it?
你会觉得我很王八蛋算了别说了
You're gonna think I'm anasshole. Let's Just forget about it.
拜托  艾瑞克  你知道我们是无话不谈的
Come on,Erik, you know you can talk to me about anything.
好吧
All right.
嘿咻
It's thesex.
我是说
I mean,
我们在一起两年了两年  崔西
we've been together for two years. Two years, Trace.
我们高一时还无所谓
I mean,when we were Juniors, it was one thing,
可是现在高三了  你还守身如玉
but we're seniorsnow, and this whole virgin thing
这开始产生很严重的后果
is starting to have someserious consequences.
我是说你害我杀了人
I mean,people are dying.
-我说过我还没准备好  -我早已准备好了
-I toldyou, I'mnot ready yet. -I am so ready.
我准备好不就表示两人都准备好了吗?
Can't Ibe readyenough for the both of us?
-不应该这样说  -应该
-It doesn't workthat way. -It should.
对不起艾瑞克  我知道你一直很有耐心
I'm sorry, Erik.I know how patient you've been.
我知道只是有时候...
I know.It's Justsometimes...
怎样?
What?
你是女孩你要做处女很容易
Well, you're a girl. It'sa lot easier for you to be a virgin
因为你做处女越久感觉就似乎越纯洁
becausethe longer you stay a virgin, the more pure and innocent you seem.
我做处男越久
The longer I staya virgin,
就越成为全校的笑柄
the moreI becomethe laughingstock of the entire school.
对不起可是...我是说...
I'm sorry, but...I mean...
很抱歉提到这个
I'm sorry I brought it up.
我得走了放学后见
I gottago. I'llsee youafter school.
好
Okay.
再见
Bye.
告诉你他的老二有这么大
I'm telling you,his dickwas this big.
艾瑞克呢?  他的一定很大吧
What about Erik?I bet he's got a big one.
崔西可不知道
Well, Tracy wouldn't know.
随便你
Whatever.
不真枪实弹来  我想也很难知道老二的尺寸吧
Yeah, Iguess it's prettyhard to figure out dick size from dry humping.
布鲁克你好毒
Brooke,that's mean.
我可不像你一样  有一本全校男生老二的目录
Just because I don't havea catalog of the school's dick sizes like you,
不过这不表示我一无所知
doesn'tmean I don't knowa thing or two.
好  那艾瑞克的有多大?
Okay, sohow bigis Erik's?
-看吧?我就说  -拜托  布鲁克
-see? Told you. -Come on,Brooke.
我们之间不是那样的
It's notlike that with us.
艾瑞克与众不同  他尊重我设下的界线
I mean,Erik's different.He respects my boundaries.
你最好让他有理由留在你身边
Well, you bettergive that boy a reason to stick around,
不然他会找个界线更宽松的女孩
or he'sgonna find a girlwith looser boundaries.
-艾瑞克才不会那样 -你以前就是这样说川特的
-Erik would neverdo that. -Yeah, that's what you said about Trent.
他因为嘿休的问题而跟你分手那时是高二
He brokeup withyou oversex, and that was sophomore year.
如果不上床  那我们就分手吧
Yeah, this Just isn't gonna work without the sex.
天哪  川特好帅  听说他刚刚跟哈莉分手
God, Trent is cute, and Iheard he Just broke up with Holly.
崔西  我们都喜欢你
Look, Tracy, we love you,
也喜欢艾瑞克  可是你要看清事实
and we love Erik,but let's get real.
他是男人男人有某种需要
He's a guy, and guys havecertain needs.
真的  就像原始人一样
They really do. It's likea caveman thing or something.
我真不敢相信你能把他绑在身边那么久
Yeah, Ican't believe you've kept him tied up this long.
-嘿  艾瑞克  你猜我刚刚跟谁聊?  -谁?
-Hey, Erik, guesswho I Just talked to? -Who?
你在密西根的史提夫家表哥
Your cousin Stifler up atMichigan.
-你为什么跟我表哥杜埃特聊?  -我们常常聊啊
-Why Areyou talking to my cousin Dwight? -Oh, we talk all the time.
什么?  我们有很多相似处
What? Wehave a lot in common.
那个王八羔子想干嘛?
What's that crazybastardup to?
他是一个兄弟会的成员  这些人只会喝酒干炮
He's insome fraternity,and all those guys do is drink and fuck.
刚好这个周末他们要开个超级大派对
And it Just so happens that they're throwing a monster party this weekend
-一英里裸奔  -什么叫一英里裸奔?
-For theNaked Mile. -What's the Naked Mile?
噢  就是几千个学生裸体
Oh, dude, it's this thingwhere thousands of students
跑过校园
run naked throughcampus.
他们考完试要发泄一下
It's theway of blowing off steam after exams.
几千个裸女?
Thousands of naked chicks?
史提夫说这个派对将名留青史
Stiflersays thatthis party is gonna be epic.
反正  这个地方太无聊
Bottom line is, this place is played out.
高中我们已经玩腻了
High school's over for us.
应该另外找地方寻乐
It's time to plant our flag in a new land.
A片  射精害死奶奶  永久禁足?
Porn, cumshot, dead grandmother, grounded for ever?
别担心
Don't worry.
告诉你爸妈说
Just tell your parents that, you know,
你想去念那个学校
you're thinking about going to school there.
-不太好吧 -拜托
-I don'tknow, man. -Oh,please.
你告诉你妈说要去波士顿念书时  她哭了
Your momcried when you told her you were going to school in Boston.
如果她觉得让你离家比较近的话
She'll probably help youpack
她也许会帮你打包
if she thinks it'll keepyou close to home.
我帮你打包
I'll help you pack.
我做三明治
I'll make sandwiches.
-鸡肉沙拉?  -好啊
-Chickensalad? -Of course.
你有机会跟你的表哥见面吗?
Are yougonna geta chance to see your cousin?
有  我们可能会路过打个招呼
Yeah. Wemight stop by and say hello.
你应该多跟他学学
Now, there's someone youshould definitely look up to.
我想他一定没有时间往自己家人身上射精
I bet hedoesn'thave time to blow his load on his family.
-哈瑞  拜托  -我不懂
-Harry,please. -I don'tunderstand.
我在你这个年纪时玩女人玩得不亦乐乎
When I was your age, I was up to my neck in poontang.
根本没有时间自慰
I didn'thave time to spank my monkey.
谢谢你让我想像到一个  很恶心的画面  爸
Thank you for that very disturbing image, Dad.
我是说史提夫家的人才不会装病留在家里自慰
I mean,Stiflersdo not fake being sick to stay home and pull dick.
我们会跷课去把妹子
We cut class to get ass.
我知道我们家族就是这样
Yes, I know. Thatsayingis on our family crest.
别忘了把泻药带去
Oh, don't let meforget to pack the lmodium AD.
免得你拉肚子
You know, Just incase you get diarrhea.
-妈  -我好兴奋
-Mom. -Iam so excited.
-你不兴奋吗  哈瑞?  -我很兴奋
-Aren'tyou excited, Harry? -I'm very excited.
你别太兴奋
Don't you get excited.
跟你说的一样
It worked just like you said.
她帮我打包  还帮我做三明治
she's helping mepack, and she's even making us sandwiches.
-鸡肉沙拉?  -对
-Chickensalad? -Yup.
棒
sweet.
我就说嘛别怀疑我
see, I told you.Never doubt me.
这个周末要爽翻天了我等不及要跟史提夫见面
Man, this weekendis gonna be tits. I can't wait to see Stifler.
你怎么从来没叫我史提夫?
Hey, howcome younever call me Stifler?
你比较像艾瑞克
You're more of anErik.
等等
Hold on.
-那是崔西我最好接  -好再见
-That'sTracy. I'd bettertake it. -All right, later.
嘿  甜心今天的事我实在...
Hey, sweetie. Listen, about today, I'm really...
艾瑞克我要跟你上床
Erik, Iwanna have sex.
你说什么?
Excuse me?
我要上床
I wannahave sex.
-真的? -当然
-Are Youserious? -Absolutely.
你是不是在多边通话?
Do you have me ona conference call?
如果是的话  那就太差劲了
Becauseif you do, that is so not cool.
艾瑞克我不是开玩笑
Erik, this isn'ta Joke.
我要上床
I want to have sex.
好!  好好
Yes! Yes, yes.
-今晚  -什么?
-Tonight. -What?
今晚  我今晚要上床
Tonight.I wannahave sextonight.
你要我怎么出门?
How am Isupposedto getout of my house?
随便你
That's up to you.
不过午夜时我会在我家地下室
But at midnight,I'll bein my basement
等着你来蹂躏
waitingto be ravished.
我会等着
I'll bethere.
伪君子
Hypocrite.
你去弄啤酒和大麻我负责笑气
So you get the beer and the weed, and I'll handle the nitrous.
-好  艾瑞克带什么?  -三明治
-You gotit. What's Erikbringing? -Sandwiches.
好  鸡肉沙拉和大学女生
Nice. Chicken salad and college pussy.
我最喜欢的组合
My favorite combination.
对啊  至少你吃得到鸡肉沙拉
Yeah, well, at least you'll get to taste the chicken salad.
你想艾瑞克现在在干嘛?
Hey, what do youthink Erik's doing right now?
也许在对着捡来的A片打枪
Probablybeatingoff to dumpster porn.
不再对捡来的A片打枪  不再被笑话是处男
No morebeating off to dumpster porn. No more virgin Jokes.
今晚  艾瑞克史提夫将成为男人
Tonight,Erik Stifler becomes a man.
嗨
Hi.
-好  听好 -不
-All right, listen. -No.
不要说话
No talking.
-等等  -什么?
-Wait. -What?
你听到了吗?
Did youhear something?
别担心我爸妈都睡死了
No. Don't worry,my parents are passed out.
真的?  你知道我的肚子不好
Are yousure? Youknow how my stomach gets.
我帮你放松
Here, I'll help you relax.
你带了东西来吧?
You brought something, right?
干  我忘了带
Oh, shit. I leftit at home.
我可以跑回去拿  只要五...
I can run back and get it. I'll be back in like five...
别担心我有一个
No, no,don't worry. I'vegot one.
你来戴还是我来?
Do you wanna putit on orshould l?
我们一起戴上
Let's put it on together.
你准备好了吗?
Are youready?
好了
Yeah.
糟糕  有人来了  快躲到吧台后面!
Shit. someone's coming. Quick, get behind the bar. Now!
甜心  你怎么还没睡?
Honey, what are you stilldoing up?
瑜珈
Yoga.
晚餐吃太多
I ate too much atdinner.
-怎么不吃点胃散? -婴儿才吃胃散
-Why don't you take an Alka-seltzer? -Alka-seltzer is for babies.
我喝点酒就好
I Just need a nightcap.
对不起
Excuse me.
好像你才需要胃散
Sounds like you could usean Alka-seltzer.
爸  我来帮你拿酒
Daddy. Here, letme get you your drink.
不用了甜心  你继续做瑜珈吧
No, that's okay,honey. You go back to your yoga.
不  爸我来帮你拿
No, Daddy, I really wantto.
甜心  我是个大人我可以自己拿酒
Sweetie,I'm a grown man.I can make my own drink.
那是什么?
What wasthat?
什么什么?
What waswhat?
我没听到
I didn'thear anything.
洗衣房有声音
There was a noisecomingfrom the laundry room.
我一定听错了
I must be hearingthings.
我就说嘛爸  喝你的酒吧
See, Daddy? I told you. Now, come make your drink.
搞什么...
What the...
你没事吧宝贝?
You allright, baby?
我没事爸
I'm fine, Daddy.
那个变态的王八蛋在我们的干衣机里大便
Oh, thatsick bastard took a shit in our dryer.
我去叫警察
I'm calling the police.
莱恩?  莱恩?
Ryan? Ryan?
-莱恩  起来  莱恩!  -搞屁啊?
-Ryan, get up man. Ryan! -What the fuck?
是我  艾瑞克
It's me.It's Erik.
你怎么光屁股在我房间里?
Dude, why are younaked in my room?
老二上还戴着保险套
And witha rubberon yourdick.
抱歉
Oh, yeah. sorry about that.
我麻烦大了  我要你帮忙
Look, I'm in serious trouble, okay? I need your help.
那是什么味道?
What's that smell?
-你踩到狗屎吗?  -对
-Did Youstep indog shit? -Yeah.
谢谢你借我衣服  我会还给你的
Hey, man, thanksfor theclothes. I'll get them back to you.
不用了你干脆烧掉吧?
No, thanks. Why don't youJust burn them?
不知道我如果检举你能不能拿赏金
Wonder if I get arewardfor turning you in.
如果查证属实
If the alleged improprieties are confirmed,
这对白宫将是严重的打击
it couldbe devastating for the white House.
与政府接近的消息来源
Sourcesnear theadministration
对于这项指控不予证实  也不否认
would neither confirm nordeny the allegations.
至于当地新闻  一名戴着面具的窃贼闯入民宅
And in local news, a masked burglar broke into an area residence,
在该户人家的干衣机里拉屎
defecated in thefamily'sdryer,
然后向一名青少女暴露私处
and thenexposedhimselfto a teenage girl.
警方仍在继续搜索中
Police are continuing thesearch,
不过该名嫌犯的下落与身份仍然不明
but thewhereabouts and identity of the perpetrator are unknown.
这人怎么这样?
What iswrong with thesepeople?
接下来请夏大雪为我们播报气象
And now,Dakota snow withthe weekend forecast.
我不知道
I don'tknow.
-你吓到我了  -对不起
-You scared me. -sorry.
昨晚的事...
Listen,about last night...
我想还是不要提吧
Yeah, you know, I'd Justreally rather not talk about it.
我想应该提
I reallythink that we should.
艾瑞克你在我的干衣机里大便
Erik, you took acrap inmy dryer.
我被你爸吓到了
Your dadscared the shitout of me.
-等等  -我们不如...
-Wait. -You know,let's Just...
把这件事忘掉  好吧?
Let's forget about it, okay?
好  那另一件事呢?
Okay, but what about theother thing?
上床?
The sex?
我想昨晚的事是天意
I'm taking last night asa sign from above.
可是  如果你爸没有下来的话...
But maybe... I mean, if your dad didn't come down...
艾瑞克我爱你  不过
Erik, Ilove you.I'm Just...
我还没有准备好
I'm notready yet.
真的?
Really?
真的
Really.
但我知道你早已准备好
But I also reAllzed Justhow ready you are.
-我不希望因为性而分手  -我想我们不需要
-I don'twanna break up over sex. -I don't think we have to.
我没有准备好
I'm notready.
而你准备好了  我把你绑住实在很自私
You are.It's selfish forme to keep you tied down.
所以我有个建议
So, thisis whatI'm proposing.
这个周末你去尽情狂欢
A guilt-free passfor this weekend.
那表示随便你要做什么都可以
That means you can do whatever you want up there
我绝不怪你
with noconsequences.
你是说真的?
You're sure aboutthis?
我觉得爱与性不一定要彼此牵制
I don'tthink love and sex have to be tied to each other, so
所以我没有关系
I'm okaywith this.
就一个周末  好好发泄一下
One weekend. Getit out of your system,
然后回到我身边
and comeback tome.
你想考验我吗?
Is thissome kindof a test?
完全不是
Not at all.
-...一箱啤酒  -好
-...andone of bomb beer. -Yes.
这真是完美
See, this is perfect.
都好了吗?
Hey, weall set?
不知道
I don'tknow.
我就说他孬种
I told you he'd puss out.
至少三明治带了吧
Tell meyou at least brought the sandwiches.
-有问题吗?  -没问题
-What'sthe problem? -There is no problem.
崔西让我这个周末尽情狂欢
Tracy Just gave me a guilt-free pass for the weekend,
也就是说我可以为所欲为
which means I cando anything I want.
为所欲为?
Anything?
你是说...
You mean...
对  她说爱与性不一定要互相牵制
Yeah, she said that loveand sex don't have to be linked.
她要我好好发泄
she wants me to get it out of my system.
你的女朋友一下子从最差劲变成最劲爆
Dude, your girlfriend Just went from the lamest to the coolest in one shot.
你们觉得她是在考验我吗?
You guysthink itcould be, like, some sort of a test?
-不是  -不是
-No, no.-No, no.
崔西是个聪明的女孩
Tracy'sa smart girl.
她够成熟知道你是个男人...
she's mature enough to see that you're a man...
-对  -...而且你有某些需要
-Yeah. -...and you have certain needs.
-你真的这样觉得? -当然
-You think so? -Absolutely.
你开车
You're driving.
上车  我们随便找人就上
Now getin the car so wecan go get you some random pussy.
各位先生现在是星期五下午油箱加满了油
Gentlemen, it's Friday afternoon, we've got a full tank of gas,
有四分之一盎司的大麻  三箱啤酒
a quarter ounce of weed,three cases of beer,
4.5公斤的笑气  而且我们不到法定年龄
a ten-pound tankof nitrous, we're underage...
而且我醉到无法开车
And I amtoo drunk to drive.
走吧
Hit it.
你确定这东西安全吗?
You surethis shit's safe?
跟其他用来制作动物标本  的化学药品一样安全
It's assafe as any otherchemical used to freeze-dry animals.
-你看那只鸡好大 -哪里?
-Look atthe sizeof thatfucking chicken. -Where?
-搞什么啊?  -哪里有鸡啊?
-Whoa, what the fuck? -What fucking chicken?
别担心他产生幻觉了
Relax, he's hallucinating.
你发疯了吗?
Are youout of your fucking mind?
对啊  崔西  你怎么能这样?
Yeah, Tracy. Whatwere you thinking?
你们不是说我应该给他一个留在我身边的理由
But youguys toldme I had to give him a reason to stick around.
对  你要给他理由
Yeah, you give him a reason,
不是摆明让他去疯狂一个周末
not givehim a free passto go have a weekend orgy.
你一定要阻止他
You've got to stop this.
如果他这个周末跟别人上床
lf he has sex this weekend,
你觉得接下来会怎样?
what doyou think's gonnahappen?
他就能发泄一下
That itwill getit out of his system.
这样就好了
Oh, yeah. That'show it works.
他会吃完大鱼大肉后回来吃小菜
He's gonna go from getting laid back to dry humping.
这很冒险崔西
It's pretty risky, Tracy.
冒险?  这根本就是打开潘朵拉的盒子
Risky? It's a fucking Pandora's box, literally.
他一旦玩过了盒子里面  柔嫩的粉红色天鹅绒
And oncehe's felt the soft pink velvet on the inside of the box,
他就不会再满足于用老二磨磨盒盖
he's notgonna goback torubbing his dick on the outside of the lid.
我可没这样想过
Never thought ofit likethat.
崔西  男人就像狗
Tracy, men are like dogs
什么东西都想干
that runaround and humpanything they see.
赶快去拿狗链把你的狗拴起来
Now go and get your dog back on its leash.
拜托  艾瑞克
Come on,Erik.
我就知道没这么好的事
I knew it was toogood tobe true.
抱歉  各位  这是为大家好
sorry, kids. It'sfor thebest.
崔西?
Tracy?
噢  李文斯汀先生
Oh, Mr.Levenstein.
-嗨  -嗨
-Hi. -Hi.
你回来上瑜珈课了
You're back for more yoga.
我太太迷上了
Well, mywife ishooked on it,
她觉得如果我灵活一点的话
and shethinks ifI can be a little more flexible,
我们就能尝试新的...
we can try some new...
你听过一本书叫《Kama  sutra》吗?
Have youever heard of abook called the Kama sutra?
没有
No.
我太太刚买的
Oh, well, my wifeJust got it,
里面有些动作需要大力伸展才做得到
and there's somestuff inthere that requires some serious stretching,
你知道我的意思吧
if you know whatI mean.
你还好吗?  你好像有点不高兴
Are youokay, honey? Youlook a little upset.
只是跟男友呕气
Oh, youknow, Just some boyfriend stuff.
噢  男朋友
Oh, boyfriend stuff.
希望我能帮得上忙
Well, ifthere'sanythingI can do.
别误会不过我想你是不会了解的
No offense or anything, but I don't think you'd understand.
哦  我知道了
Oh, I see.
我的儿子也曾经有许多
You know, my sonhad hisfair share
与交往性生活
of relationshiplsexuall
馅饼有关的问题
pastry-related difficulties,
多年来我的开导对他助益良多
and I think my advice helped him over the years.
一个女孩子笨到给她的处男朋友
Well, doyou haveany advice for a girl dumb enough to
整个周末尽情狂欢的许可证
give her virginboyfriend
你能给她什么建议吗?
a guilt-free passfor theweekend?
什么  尽情狂欢的许可证?
I'm sorry, a guilt-free pass?
也就是说这个周末他可以
That means he could do whatever
为所欲为不用承担后果
he wantsthis weekend with no consequences.
天哪!
Oh my!
听起来很进步
Well, that certainly sounds progressive,
我想这也许会是个很无聊的周末
and a safe bet onwhat isprobably gonna be a humdrum weekend.
这个周末是一英里裸奔
He's atthe NakedMile this weekend.
你让男朋友到一英里裸奔去尽情狂欢?
You gaveyour boyfriend aguilt-free pass to the Naked Mile?
你开什么玩笑?
Are youkiddingme?
崔西  一英里裸奔很疯狂  你...
Tracy, the NakedMile isinsane. You...
我是听来的  我当然没有亲身经历过
From what I hear.I wouldn't know from personal experience
因为我跟这个一点关系也没有
becausel, you know, I have nothing whatsoever to do with it.
可是  崔西
But, look, Tracy,
即使你的男朋友去一英里裸奔
even ifyour boyfriend isat this Naked Mile,
他也不见得会做什么
it doesn't mean he's gonna do anything.
真的?
Really?
他有能力做  不表示一定会去做
Well, Just because he can, doesn't mean he will.
男女交往首重信任
Relationships areall about trust.
我想你说的对
Yeah, Iguess you're right.
-再见  -再见
-Well, namaste. -Namaste.
-你看到我的手机吗?  -没有
-Hey, have you seen my phone? -No.
也许你把它留在学校了
Maybe you left itback atschool.
没有  我以为我放在背包里
No, no,I thoughtI put in my backpack.
前面的休息站停一下好吗?我要小便
Hey, youwanna pull overat that stop up ahead? I gotta take a piss.
尿在罐子里啦
Just piss in a can or something.
老二会被盖子割到
Man, I could cutmy dickon the lip.
那就向窗外小便
Well, piss out the window.
湖边的微风多好
Love that breezeoff thelake.
这里真棒
This place is incredible.
想想看我明年就要来这里念书了
Just think, nextyear I'mgonna be going here.
对啊  还好你老爸跟校友会有关系
Yeah, thanks to Daddy andhis alumni connections.
少废话我是成绩好
Fuck off. I toldyou, I got in on my SAT scores.
你比低能儿的成绩好五分而已
You scored five points above being legally retarded.
随便你反正我申请到了
Whatever. still got in.
这里怎么有尿臊味?
Hey, whydoes itsmell like piss back here?
这里就是贝塔兄弟会
This isit. BetaDelta Xi.
-就是这里?  -对
-This isthe house? -Yeah.
酷
Cool.
哇靠
Whoa.
-这里在干嘛?  -谁知道
-What'sgoing onhere? -Ihave no idea.
喝  喝喝  喝
Drink. Drink. Drink. Drink.
别吐!
Hold your drink!
好
Okay.
Yeah.
你觉得怎样  小高?
How youfeeling there, stretch?
有点头昏?
Little dizzy?
你知道吗?
Causeguess what?
史提夫可以一整天喝这个
Stiflercan drinkthis shit all day long.
史提夫!
Stifler!
你表哥真是我的偶像
Your cousin is myhero.
-好  大家不要动! -糟了
-All right, everybody freeze! -Oh, shit.
校园警卫
Campus security.
谁也不准喝
Nobody takes another drink...
让我先下注  200元赌史提夫赢!
...tillI got mybet down. I got $200 on Stifler!
史班奇你吓我一跳王八蛋
spanky,you had me going,you silly son of a bitch.
来!  来!
Let's doit. Do it!
好
Yeah.
我得承认你够厉害
You gotsteel nuts, my man. I'll give you that much.
不过你不是史提夫的对手
But you're no match for the stif-man.
干你妈的史提夫
Fuck you, Stifler.
耶
Yeah.
怎么了小白脸?
What's the matter, Boy Band?
你要吃胃散吗?
You needa littlesomething to settle your stomach?
喝喝史提夫的酒
Yeah, take in theStifleressence.
好呛
Mighty pungent.
耶!
Yeah!
世界重量级饮酒大赛冠军
And still Heavyweight Drinking Champion of the World,
还是铁肝杜埃特史提夫!
Dwight The lronLiverStifler!
我他妈的太行了!
I'm a bad motherfucker, baby!
他没事他没事
He's okay. He's okay.
嘿  表弟
Hey, cousin.
你好吗?
How youdoing?
没事  杜埃特  你没事吧?
I'm fine, Dwight.Are youokay?
我没事
Oh, yeah, I'm fine.
没事
I'm fine.
我听说你射精把奶奶给射死了
Hey, I heard thatyou killed Grandma with your cumshot.
真差劲
That sucks, man.
-要不要带他去医院?  -他没事的
-Shouldwe take him to the hospital? -No, he'll be fine.
他告诉我他一个月这样喝一次
He toldme he does this,like, once a month.
你们照顾他一下  我去厕所
Okay, well, you guys keepan eye on him. I'm gonna go to the bathroom.
我当然是要去啦  那是一英里裸奔耶!
Yes, I'mgoing. It's thenaked mile!
我们什么时候开始派对?
So, whenare we gonna start partying?
有人开始春心荡漾了
Oh, someone's feeling a little frisky.
我终于决定不再辜负我的家族传统了
Let's Just say Ifinallydecided to live up to the family name.
史提夫?大事不妙了
Stifler?We got aseriousproblem, man.
麦克跟其他人想从动物园偷猴子  刚刚被捕了
Mike andthe guysJust got arrested trying to steal a monkey from the zoo.
那有什么问题?
so what's the problem?
从我的保释基金里拿钱出来就好了
Just take the money out of my bail fund.
几乎半个足球队都被逮了
They'realmost half our football team.
我们要能出场比赛才行  否则就完蛋了
We gottaput a team on the field, man, or we're done.
-为什么? -因为我们已经变成候补队了
-Why? -Cause we're already on probation.
一定要参加每一场校内比赛
We gottaparticipate in every intermural event
否则就会被踢出校园
or we'rekicked off campus, man.
我们少了四个人
We're four guys short.
我会踢足球
I play football.
我高一时踢过
I playedfreshmanyear.
你呢?
What about you?
偶尔玩玩
A littleNerf here and there.
够了  史提夫?
Good enough. Stifler? Mmm?
你能上场吗?
Can youplay?
绝不要怀疑
Don't ever
史提夫是否能上场
ask if Stifler can play.
我没事
I'm good.
我们这队已经连续五年没有被打败过
The teamwe're playing'sbeen undefeated five straight years.
这些人一定很认真
These guys must be prettyserious.
没错  他们很认真
Fucking-A-right,they'reserious.
蓝达兄弟会
Lambda Pi Gamma.
他们在各方面都是我们的死对头
They'reour archrivals in everything
运动  女人  喝酒都是
sports,women, booze.
这些人很邪恶
These guys are fucking evil.
-准备好!-来!
-Get ready! -Comeon!
蹲下!
Down!
蓝色42
Blue 42.
他们是侏儒
They'remidgets.
开始!
Hut!
别小看了他们的身材
Don't let their size fooIyou.
这些人猛得很
These guys are fucking animals.
我是不是笑气吸太多了?  侏儒兄弟会?
Did I dotoo muchnitrous? A midget fraternity?
广告里面的那些有钱的侏儒
Those rich midgets from those infomercials
捐了一大笔钱给学校
gave theschool some hugegrant,
开办了一个侏儒学院和兄弟会
and started a school forthe vertically challenged and a fraternity.
美国的每个侏儒都想来这里
And thisis whereevery midget in America wants to be.
热腿!
Hot feet!
没错
That's right.
分解动作
Breakdown.
这些人是人中之龙
These guys are the best of the best.
我说是谁呢
Well, well, well.
原来是一般高的低能儿还有低能队长
lf it isn't the regular-size retards and Captain Retard himself.
你又准备吃败仗了史提夫?
You ready to getyour asskicked again, shitler?
回到绿野仙踪的乐园去吧
Get backto Oz there
免得你被我们痛宰一顿  小托托
before you get your ass stomped, Toto.
托托是那只狗  你白痴啊
Toto wasthe dog,you fucking idiot.
舔我懒趴吧  你这马戏团的废物侏儒
Lick myballs, big-wheel-riding, midget motherfucker.
是小矮人你这废物
It's little person, fuck-nut.
今年我要啃你的另一只腿
This year, I'm gonna takea chunk out of your other leg.
你这小...
You little...
-你要吗?你要吗?来啊 -别打了
-You want it? Youwant it? Come on. -Take it easy.
哇赛
Whoa. Whoa.
滚开  王八蛋
Out of my way, assholes.
那人怎么搞的?
What's that guy'sproblem?
那是洛克他有神经病
That's Rock. He'sfuckingcrazy.
-他会使诈 -你这白痴
-He plays dirty. -You fucking idiot.
-去年  他把我腿上的肉咬掉一块  -天哪!
-Last year, he bit a chunk out of my thigh. -Jesus!
他的女朋友蛮辣的
Hey, hisgirlfriend's pretty hot.
那个正常人是怎么回事?
Yeah. And what'swith that regular-size guy?
喔  那是洛克的表弟
Oh, it'sRock's cousin.
他们得让他加入  因为他是一家人
They hadto let him in. Legacy.
真是饭桶
What a douchebag.
他打得好吗?
Can he play?
很差
No, he sucks.
注意喔
Hey, keep your head up.
他们是侏儒  又能怎样?
Whatever, they'remidgets. How bad can it be?
妈的!
Holy shit!
小心喔婊子
Keep your head up, bitch.
我就说不要小看这些小王八蛋
I told you, man.Don't underestimate these little bastards.
蹲下!
Down!
准备!
set!
开始!
Hut!
耶!
Yeah!
-贝塔!-来!
-Beta! -Come on!
大家加油到线上去
Let's go, fellas.Get onthe line.
蹲下!
Down!
你觉得如何  史提夫?
How youfeeling,Stifler?
我身高185  你呢佛罗多?
I'm 6'1, Frodo.How about you?
准备!
set!
开始!
Hut!
这个小杂种又在咬我了
The little fucker's biting me again.
别碰我眼睛!
Not in my eye!
奇怪  我看你不像身高185废料
Funny, you don'tlook 6'1from here, shit stain.
我恨那个人
I hate that fucking guy.
我快在场上毙命了
I'm getting killed out there.
我逃不过他
I can'tget loose.
他们又小又快  我不知道该怎么办
They'reso fast and small. I don't know what to do.
别哭了你们这些没用的货色
Quit crying, youbunch ofbra-wearing pussies.
我腿上刚刚被咬掉一块肉  你们也没听到我在抱怨
I Just got a hunktaken out of my leg. You don't hear me crying.
好吧  大家尽力而为
All right, then,let's put our balls on the table.
大家加油让这些小王八蛋
Let's goout there and show these little sons of bitches
尝尝贝塔队的厉害
what being a Beta's all about.
-大家听到我的话了吗?  -听到了
-You understand what I'msaying, fellas? -Yeah, yeah.
好  数到三说贝塔
All right, Beta on three.
-一  二三  贝塔!  -贝塔!
-One, two, three,Beta! -Beta!
-蹲下!-准备!
-Down! -set!
开始!
Hut!
冲!
Go!
对  大家加油
Yeah, yeah. Let'sgo, boys.
好  我们剩下五秒
All right, we gotfive seconds left, guys.
如果你们要被擒抱了就向后传给最近的人
lf you're about to get tackled, lateral it to the nearest guy.
这是我们唯一的机会
It's ouronly chance.
好  加油来吧  数到三
All right, let'sgo now.Come on, Beta on three.
-数到三 -谁跟我?
-Beta onthree. -Who's with me?
-一  二三  贝塔!  -贝塔!
-One, two, three,Beta! -Beta!
蹲下!
Down!
准备!
Set!
开始!
Hut!
我们痛宰了你们一顿!
We kicked your ass!
你还是没我厉害  史提夫
You're still my bitch, Stifler.
耶!
Yeah!
我不敢相信我们输给侏儒
I can'tbelieve we lost to midgets.
别生那些小矮子的气
Don't let those Oompa Loompa bastards get to you.
我们现在还有更重要的事要做各位
Right now, we have more important matters to tend to, gentlemen.
就我所知
From what I understand,
我表弟得到尽情狂欢的许可
my cousin has a guilt-free pass
可以跟他想要的任何女孩嘿咻
to bangall the girls hecan find.
没错
That I do.
真是好消息
Oh, thatis goodnews.
一开始我还以为你是领养的
Christ,for a while I wasstarting to think you were adopted.
各位
Gentlemen,
欢迎来到天堂
welcometo paradise.
男孩女孩
Boys andgirls,
我们之中有一位名人
we havea celebrity in our midst.
就是全世界重量级饮酒比赛冠军
The Heavyweight DrinkingChampion of the World,
铁肝杜埃特史提夫!
Dwight lron LiverStifler!
好  你们这些屁蛋我要去找些马子
All right, you pussy-wipes, I'm gonna go find some lady friends.
尽量不要一分钟就射出来  好吗?
Try notto blow your wadin the first minute, huh?
艾力森的派对绝没有比吉米的棒
There isno way Allison'sparty was better than Jimmy's.
你发疯啊吉米的派对有两桶啤酒
You're nuts. Jimmy's party had two kegs
那两个搞剧场的女孩在撞球桌上  在大家面前
and those two theater chicks went down on each other on the pooI table
互相口交
in frontof everybody.
-你们两个在说什么?  -什么?
-What the hell are you two talking about? -What?
两桶啤酒搞剧场的女孩  你们猜怎样?
Two kegs, theaterchicks.Well, guess what?
我们在大学酒吧里这里有无尽的酒和女人
We're ina college bar full of unlimited booze and pussy,
我们却坐在吧台聊高中派对
and we're sittingat thebar talking about high-school parties.
莱恩?  莱恩!  你怎么搞的?
Ryan? Ryan! What's your problem?
大富高中有什么了不起
That Great Fallsattitude.
你们提到大富高中
All youguys do is talk about Great Falls
好像没什么比那里厉害一样
like it's the end -All andbe-all of existence.
呆在那里根本没有出息  所以我才要去加州
The place is a fucking trap, which is why I'm going to callfornia.
我不要像其他人一样被困在那里
I'm notgonna getstuck like the rest of them.
对  我知道  我觉得这样很好
Yeah, Iknow. I think that's great.
对  可是你没看到吗?
Yeah, but don't you see?
这个周末对我来说就是这个意义
That's what thisweekendis about for me.
-什么意义?  -看看我能否做到
-What doyou mean? -To see if I can do it.
是否能重新开始  接受我菜鸟的地位
lf I canstart over and accept being low man on the totem pole.
莱恩  这只是一个周末而已
Ryan, it's Just aweekend, man.
也许对你是如此  不过对我远不只如此
Maybe toyou, butto me it's a lot more than that.
我听起来简直像个女人
Man, I sound likea chick.
-我实在需要去找个女人  -对
-Mmm-hmm. I really need to go get some pussy. -Yeah.
-干  -天哪  对不起
-Oh, shit. -Oh, my God. I'm so sorry.
-没关系 -我真是笨手笨脚
-No, no,no, no.It's fine. -I can't believe I did that.
跟我来
Here, come with me.
-快把衬衫脱掉  -你说什么?
-Quick,take offyour shirt. -Excuse me?
-我要把油渍洗掉 -对
-Well, IJust...I wannaget the stain out. -Oh, yeah, right.
我就知道
I knew that.
我们可以呆在这后面吗?
Are we allowed tobe backhere?
可以  别担心  我以前在这里调过酒
Oh, yeah, don't worry. Iused to bartend here.
酷
Cool.
我真的非常抱歉
Look, I'm really,reallysorry about this. Right.
你只是一时不小心
Accidents happen.
-我叫布兰迪  -我是艾瑞克
-I'm Brandy, by the way.-I'm Erik.
如果我把饮料洒在兄弟会其他的王八蛋身上
You know, any other fratasshole
他们一定会对我
would bite my head off right now
很不爽
if I spilled a drink on him.
我...
I'm...
我不是兄弟会的人
I'm notin a fraternity.
你不是?你是无党派?
Oh, you're not? so you'reindependent?
-什么叫无党派?  -就是非兄弟会的学生
-What'sthat? -You know,a student who's not Greek.
我只是周末来玩  我是高三学生
No, I'mJust visiting forthe weekend. I'm a senior in high school.
-高中? -对
-High school? -Yeah.
真的?
Really?
我这样说的时候  大部分女生都会打我或踢我
Most girls slap me or kick me in the balls when I say that.
为什么?真好笑
Why? It's hysterical.
我也是这样觉得  你叫什么名字?
That's what I say. What are your names?
我是吉儿她是爱蕾克斯
I'm Jilland thisis Alexis.
这是我朋友莱恩
Hey, this is my buddy Ryan.
-嗨  莱恩 -嗨  莱恩
-Hey, Ryan. -Hey,Ryan.
嗨  女士们
Hey, ladies.
国际特赦组织  那是摇滚乐团吗?
Amnestylnternational. Isthat some kind of rock band?
那是一个在全球保护人权的组织
It's anorganization thatworks to protect human rights all over the world.
对了
Oh.
嘿  别想抢我们的女伴
Hey, getaway from our dates.
下面啦笨蛋
Down here, asshole.
-你们要干嘛?  -他刚刚说了
-What the hell doyou want? -Just what he said.
你们别想抢我们女伴
For youtwo to get away from our dates.
少作梦了小东西
ln yourdreams, Willow.
这些女孩不可能跟你们一起
There isno way these girls are here with you.
是吗?
Are you?
-为什么? -他们很酷
-But Why? -They're cool.
也很性感
And sexy.
你开什么玩笑
You gotta be fucking kidding me.
这里没有人开玩笑废物
Ain't nobody kidding around here, punk.
你要是不爽  我们在这里解决吧
lf you got a problem, wecould settle this right here.
好啊
Oh, I would loveto.
别闹了你们
Okay, stop it, you guys.
很高兴认识你们两位
Listen,it was really nice meeting you two,
不过我们今晚已经名花有主了
but we're spokenfor tonight.
宝贝  来跳舞吧
Come on,baby, let's dance.
怎么会这样
That didnot Justhappen.
准备帮史提夫吹吹吧
Time fora Stifler blowJob!
噢  好性感啊  我喜欢
Oh, getsexy, ladies, I love it.
我觉得胯下有点痒痒的
Oh, I feel a stirring inmy loins.
你一定要见见我的室友
You've gotta meetmy roommate.
我很愿意
I wouldlove to.
妈的  那些侏儒刚抢走我们的女人
Dude, the fuckingmidgetsJust stole our women.
对啊  那些废物太嚣张了
Yeah, those fuckers are out of hand.
我就说过别低估那些小杂种
I told you guys,don't underestimate those little bastards.
那个侏儒四分卫去年抢走我女朋友
That midget quarterback stole my girlfriend last year.
-贱!  -滚开
-Slut! -Out of mygoddamnway.
操你妈的!
Holy shit!
我以为这个地方不准输家进来的
I thought this place hada no-loser policy.
你们这些王八蛋在这里干嘛?
What are you assholes doing here?
滚开  大老鼠
Fuck off, MightyMouse.
你们的女人喜欢粗短的  不喜欢细长的
Man, don't take it out onme because your ladies like it short and thick,
可别怪我
rather than talland skinny.
洛克  你不知道吗?这个酒吧就像云霄飞车
Rock, don't you know, baby? This bar is like a roller coaster.
对  有身高限制
Yeah, ithas a height requirement,
-恐怕你还不够高 -去你妈的
-and I'mafraid you Justdon't measure up! -Motherfucker.
-别闹了!别闹了!-喂!
-Easy!Easy! Easy! -Whoa!
-咱们走着瞧  史提夫  -你说的不错
-This isn't over,shitler. -Oh, you got that right!
绝不要挡我的路  女人
Never get in my way, woman.
怎样?
What's up?
贱人
Bitch.
怎么会
That didnot happen.
我对天发誓是真的我头上罩着丝袜在街上跑
I swearto God, Iwas running through the streets with nylons on my head
保险套还戴着
and thecondom still on.
-我真不敢相信我告诉了你这件事  -我觉得很棒
-I can'tbelieveI Just told you that story. -I think it's great.
这样想吧你永远不会忘记你的第一次
I mean,think ofit thisway, you'll never forget your first time.
其实...
Well, itwasn't...
-事实上...  -等等
-Technically... -Oh, no,wait.
你是说你甚至还没有...
You meanyou didn't evenget to...
它一下子就软下来了
He camedown toofast.
谢啦  谢谢你嘲笑我的不幸
Thank you. Thankyou forlaughing at my misfortune.
我觉得你人很好  也很帅
I thinkyou're asweetheart. And you're really cute.
我就住这里
This isme.
你们明天要跑一英里吗?
so, areyou guysrunningthe Mile tomorrow?
我不知道身为处男还在街上
I don'tknow. There's something about running naked down the street
裸奔...
while you're still a virgin...
-你以前就做过  -说的也是
-Didn'tstop youbefore. -Touche.
说不定处男这件事
You never know, that virgin thing,
在周末过后就完全改变了
it couldtotallychange by the end of the weekend.
谢谢你陪我走回来
Thanks for walking me home.
昨晚你是怎么了?
What thehell happened toyou last night?
-大家怎样?  -怎样?
-What'sup, fellas? -What's up?
一些侏儒在酒吧让我们无法爽到
What's up is we got cock-blocked by some midgets at the bar.
库斯  这件事先不管你跑到哪里去了?
Cooze, never mindthat. Where the hell were you?
妈妈  如果你一定要知道的话
Well, Mother, ifyou mustknow,
我跟一个女孩在一起
I was with a girl.
胡说  哪个女孩?
Bullshit. What girl?
她叫布兰迪  她是一个姐妹会的  她辣得很
Her nameis Brandy. she'sin a sorority and she's hot,
我今晚要在一英里裸奔跟她碰面
and I'msupposedto meether at the Mile tonight.
我搞不懂
Dude, Idon't getit.
我们到大学来  女孩要侏儒不要我们
We cometo college, we get blown off by chicks for midgets,
你却跟一个姐妹会的女孩一起混?
and you're hanging out with a sorority girl?
这里是怎么搞的?
What thefuck isgoing onhere?
你想怎样?
so, whatare yougonna do?
什么意思?  他想跟那个女孩嘿休
What doyou mean?He's gonna bang that chick.
-你不要吗?  -什么?
-Aren'tyou? -What?
要
Yeah.
当然要我有尽情狂欢的许可证  干嘛不要?
Yeah, ofcourse Iwill. I'm on a guilt-free pass, why wouldn't I?
那何必迟疑?
Why thehesitation, man?
-干!你不要破宫 -我说过我要
-Oh, shit! You'renot gonna do it. -I said I'll do it.
艾瑞克你有上天赐予的本钱别糟蹋了
Erik, you've beengiven agift from above. Don't fuck it up.
-我不会的 -你会的
-I won't. -Yes, you will.
不会
No.
我要出去
l... I gotta getout of here.
-喂?  -嗨是我
-Hello?-Hey, it's me.
打电话看看你怎样
Callingto see how you'redoing.
我没事
I'm fine,
我只是在念书
I'm Juststudying.!
好
Okay.
Cool.
你们决定要参加一英里裸奔了吗?
So, didyou guysdecide if you're gonna run in the Naked Mile?
还没  不过你很了解我  我大概会临阵脱逃
No, notyet. Butyou knowme, I'll probably Just wimp out.
我是说你不需要去
I mean,you don'thave to.
我知道
Yeah, Iknow.
你没事吧?  你听起来有点怪
Are youokay? I mean, yousound a little weird.
没事
I'm fine.
我没事只想打电话说声嗨
I'm fine. I Justwanted to call and say hello.
谢啦  不过你不需要跟我报告好好去玩吧
Thanks,but you don't need to check in. I mean, go, have fun.
这个周末就是要这样
That's what thisweekend's all about.
你真好
You're the greatest.
艾瑞克史提夫
Erik Stifler.
嗨  李文斯汀先生
Hey, Mr.Levenstein.
哈罗  艾瑞克  真高兴见到你
Hello, Erik, goodto seeyou.
我自从我爸妈的新年派对之后就没见到你了
Yeah. Wow, I haven't seenyou since my parents' New Year's party,
对吧?
right?
对  你们家的新年派对真是疯狂
Yes, well, your folks really, really know how to ring in the new year.
很抱歉我爸在所有人面前  把你抓起来
Look, I'm sorry about mydad giving you that wedgie in front of everybody.
你爸从小就喜欢这样对我
Well, your dad'sbeen doing that to me since we were kids,
说来也很奇怪  我很喜欢这样被他耍
and strangely enough, I enjoy it.
你在这里做什么?
So, whatare youdoing uphere?
我以前在这里念书
Oh, well, I wentto school here
我偶尔喜欢回来
and, youknow, Ilike tocome back every now and then
看看校园
and check out thecampus.
这是我能想到的唯一理由  我想不到其他理由
That's the only reason I'm here. No other reason that I can think of.
你呢?  你在这里干嘛?
And whatabout you? Whatare you doing here?
其实这是私事
Actually, it's kind of personal.
-那就不必说了  -好
-Oh. Well, say nomore. -Okay.
-好  很高兴遇到你 -当然
-Okay, listen, good seeing you. -Yeah, for sure.
李文斯汀先生  你以前是我表哥麦特
Mr. Levenstein, you werea counselor
在高橡树乐团营的辅导员  对吧?
at tallOaks BandCamp with my cousin, Matt, right?
对  没错
Yes. Yes, I was.
顺便一提你表哥麦特需要一些辅导
And your cousinMatt needed some counseling...
-对  -我给了他一些意见
-Yeah. -...I might add. Igave him some advice.
意见  你觉得我可以
Advice.Do you think I could
告诉你一些秘密吗?
confidesomethingin you?
-当然了艾瑞克想说什么就说吧  -好
-Well, sure. Yes,Erik, anything. Anything. -Okay.
-我是处男 -好  先等一下好吗?
-I'm a virgin. -Okay, canI stop you there?
你姓史提夫  却是处男?
You're aStiflerand a virgin?
对
Yeah.
你是处男那又怎样?
Well, soyou're avirgin.What's the big deal?
前天晚上我的女朋友跟我试着...
Well, the other night, mygirlfriend and l... We tried to, you know...
对  可是他爸爸下楼来  结果我们没有机会做
Right. But her father came down before we had the chance to.
所以她对于性的看法完全改变
So she changed her mind completely about the sex,
但是她准许我这个周末尽情狂欢
but shegave me aguilt-free pass for the weekend.
你有尽情狂欢的许可证?
You gotthe guilt -free pass?
什么意思?
What doyou mean?
我是说
Well, Imean,
你面临了许多人都有的  尽情狂欢许可证的困境
you've got the old guilt-free pass dilemma.
-对  -这可棘手了
-Yeah. -It's a tough one.
我不知道你们这样年纪的人知道这种事
I didn'tthink people your age knew about that kind of stuff.
你以为我不懂这种事
I believe I knowmore about this than you think.
好  因为我不知道该怎么办
Good, because I Just don't know what to do here.
有个超辣的姐妹会女孩对我猛追
I mean,I've gotthis smoking-hot sorority girl all over me.
我的儿子吉姆
Well, you know, my son Jim
曾经历过类似的困境
went through kindof a similar dilemma.
他跟一位很漂亮
He was going outwith this very attractive
叫做娜迪雅的  国际交换学生交往
foreign-exchangestudentnamed Nadia.
对  就是他早泄的对象  对吧?
Right, right, yeah. That's the one he blew his load too early with, right?
-对  -两次
-Yes. -Twice.
-对  -在网路上
-Yes. -Over the lnternet.
-对  就是那个  -对
-yes, that's theone. -Yeah.
-除了早泄之外... -好
-Well, blowing loads aside... -Yeah.
第二年夏天  娜迪雅到海边来找吉姆
The nextsummer Nadia came to visit Jim at the beach,
他拒绝了她
and he turned herdown
因为他爱上了米雪儿
becausehe had fallen inlove with Michelle,
后来跟她结了婚  现在她是我孙女的妈妈
who he later married, andis now the mother of my grandchild.
所以  你是说我不该跟这个
So you're sayingI shouldn't
姐妹会的女孩嘿咻?
hook upwith thissorority girl?
我是说只有你自己知道该怎么做  艾瑞克
I'm saying I think only you know the answer to that, Erik.
我得走了
Well, gotta run.
噢  艾瑞克  你奶奶的事我很难过
Oh, Erik, I was sorry tohear about your grandmother.
昨晚好棒啊
Last night was amazing.
对啊
Yeah, itwas.
我们三个应该找时间再玩一次
The three of us should doit again sometime.
当然
Definitely.
朋友  你知道默瑞街怎么走吗?
Hey, buddy. You know howto get to Murray street?
知道  沿着玛里兰街一直走...
Oh, yeah, man. Just go right down Maryland, down to...
怎么...
What the...
这是什么?  侏儒过江吗?
What isthis? Enter the Midget?
我们是矮人  你这王八蛋
It's little people, asshole.
要打就来吧
Come getsome.
要打就来吧!
Come getsome, baby!
侏儒突袭史提夫
MidgetsJumped Stifler.
-啊?  -啊?
-What? -What?
侏儒突袭史提夫
The midgets Jumped Stifler.
他现在在医院
He's inthe hospital right now.
-妈的  -他娘的
-Oh, shit. -Holyshit.
他好惨
Man, heis fuckedup.
先是奶奶现在是他
First Grandma, and now this.
好  我们要让那些死侏儒好看
All right, we gotta get those fucking midgets.
对
Yeah, man.
莱恩  小声点好不好我头痛死了
Jesus, Ryan, keepit down, will you? I got a huge fucking headache.
我们以为这个人是你
We thought this guy was you.
才不是
Fuck, no.
我不知道那人怎么了
I don'tknow whathappened to that pussy.
到底怎么回事?
Hey, man, what the hell happened?
洛克跟他的一伙人突袭我  穿着黑衣和滑雪面具
Rock andhis boysJumpedme, wearing all black and ski masks.
我还会认不出来吗
Like I wouldn't know it was them.
你没事吧?  你还能裸奔吗?
Are youall right? Are you gonna be able to run in the Mile?
大概不行了
Doesn'tlook likeit.
医生说史提夫至少要再躺两天
Doc saysthe stif-man's gonna be laid up for at least a couple of more days.
别担心我们会去找那些小杂种
Hey, don't worry.We willfind those little fuckers.
你们的好意我心领了好吧?
No. I appreciateit, okay?
史提夫再去想其他的主意
Stifler'll thinkof something.
你们来这里  是要做两件事玩乐
Now youguys areup hereto do two things: Have fun,
还有跟几百个
and runnaked
又辣  奶又大  又淫荡的女人一起裸奔
with hundreds ofhot, big-breasted, horny women.
懂吗?
You understand?
-懂  -懂
-Yeah. -Yeah.
好  现在滚开  让我睡一下
Good. Now get thefuck out of here so I can get some sleep.
-嘿  艾瑞克  等一下再走 -好
-Hey, Erik, stickaroundfor a second. -Yeah.
我了解你的处境
Listen,I know what you're going through.
-你了解? -当然我在中学时
-You do? -Sure, yeah. I had the same problem
曾有过相同的问题
when I was in middle school.
但是要光祖耀宗并不容易
But living up tothe family name is not an easy thing, man.
那你是怎么做的?
Yeah. What did you do?
我对班上的人露鸟偷了校长的车
Well, Iwhipped out my dick in class, stole the principal's car,
然后跟学校餐厅的女服务生上床
and thenI fuckeda lunchlady.
-喔  -不过那只是我
-Oh. -But, hey, that's me.
你觉得我该怎么做?
What doyou thinkI should do?
我无法决定或建议你要自己去摸索
It's notfor me to decideor advise. You gotta figure that out on your own.
但我要说我们家族的人都很脱线
But I will say this. We got a pretty fucked-up family,
出了你这样的人还真好
and it'snice having a guy like you around.
现在走吧
Now, seriously, go.
我只想说
All I have to sayis,
谢谢你爸爸  你让我这个笨蛋进了这所学校
thank you, Dad, for getting my dumb ass into this school.
各位  我们正式到了目的地
Gentlemen, we have officially arrived at our destination.
看看谁来了
Look whodecidedto showup.
我就知道你们胆子不够大
I didn'tthink you guys would have the balls for this.
我没有猜错
I guessI was right.
看看  他们还穿着衣服
Check itout. They stillgot their clothes on.
臭史提夫呢?
Where isold shitler?
我想一英里裸奔之王今年来不成了
I guessthe kingof the Naked Mile didn't make it this year.
我不裸奔谁也别想裸奔!
Nobody starts this fucking Naked Mile without me!
我忠心的子民们
My loyalsubjects,
国王来了露出你们的咪咪吧!
the kinghas arrived! Bring out your titties!
你真的以为稍微打我一下  我就来不了吗?
You really thinkthat little beating you gave me could keep me away?
你跟你的棒棒糖工会打人跟五岁小孩一样
You andthe Lollypop Guild punch like a bunch of five-year-olds.
这是我的学校
This ismy fucking school.
各位
Guys.
对  别管那些人  我们是来享乐的  对吧?
Right, screw those guys.We're here to have fun, right?
废话  我们是来享乐的
Oh, fucking-A-right, we're here to have some fun.
你们怎么还穿着衣服?
Hey, whythe helldo youguys still have your clothes on?
听好  史提夫  我们在说...
Listen,Stifler,we weretalking and...
嘿  史提夫  我喜欢你的点滴
Hey, Stifler. I like yourlVs.
女士们好
Hello, ladies.
和以往一样性感
Lookingsexy as always.
听说你住院了
Heard you were inthe hospital.
被一群侏儒打了一下
Just a little beating bya bunch of midgets.
嘿  库斯
Hey, Cooze.
俏吉儿库斯又盯上你了
Jill theThrill.Back onthe Cooze radar.
嘿  艾瑞克
Hey, Erik.
嗨  布兰迪
Hey, Brandy.
-莱恩  -爱蕾克斯
-Ryan. -Alexis.
你们准备好要裸奔
So, youladies ready to run this Mile
展现超性感的身材吗?
and getextra fucking sexy?
-当然!-当然!
-Hell, yeah! -Hell, yeah!
你们男生呢?
What about you guys?
对啊  你们还穿着衣服干嘛?
Yeah, what are you guys doing still dressed?
我想我们用看的就好了
Well, wefiguredwe'd Just watch the Mile
完了后再到派对跟你们碰面
and thenmeet youguys atthe party afterwards.
真可惜这个一英里裸奔会很疯狂哟
That's too bad Cause thisNaked Mile is gonna be crazy.
真的很疯狂  对吧布兰迪?
Really crazy. Right, Brandy?
完全失控
Absolutely out ofcontrol.
对!  我就是这样想!
Yeah! That's whatI'm fucking talking about, boys.
让小鸟解放!
set thecocks free!
我们先在这里聚一下
Let's huddle up over here. Come on, fellas.
男生聚一聚
Cock huddle.
好
All right, bitchtits.
-我给你们一个惊喜的礼物 -是什么?
-I got alittle surprisefor you fuckers. -What do you got?
待会儿可以用一点药品来增加情趣
Just a little pharmaceutical delight for later.
史提夫!你没割包皮!
Stifler!You uncircumcised twat!
杰克森你的鸟好小
Jackson,you little-dicked motherfucker.
-这是什么?  -好像是摇头丸
-What isthis? -It lookslike some kind of E.
-要现在吞吗?  -他说留到待会儿再吞
-Shouldwe take it now? -He said save it for later.
别理他!我就要在大街上裸奔了
Fuck that! I'm about to run naked through the streets.
需要用药品来壮壮胆
I need all the drug-induced courage I can get.
我真高兴你们决定要跑
I'm so glad you guys decided to run.
-一定有运动吧  -有我踢足球
You mustwork out. Yeah,well, I play football.
我喜欢足球员
I love football players.
有没有人说过你的臀部很漂亮?
Did anybody evertell youthat you have a nice ass?
那个人真混帐!
That guy's a prick!
嗨  史提夫  这是不是很棒的摇头丸?
Hey, Stifler, isthis supposed to be some pretty good E?
什么摇头丸?
What E?
你给我们的药丸
The pills you gave us.
干!  你们太低能了
Oh, shit! You retards.
那不是摇头丸  那会让你勃起四个钟头
That's not E. It's that fucking four-hour hard-on drug.
-惨了  -我在医院偷拿的
-Oh, shit. -I scored someat the hospital.
我想它可以帮助  你们这些硬不起来的人
I thought you limp-dickedbitches could use some.
-天哪  -干  你没有...
-Oh, God. -Holy fuck, youdidn't...
妈的!
Holy shit!
我想我无法克制了它完全不听我的使唤
I don'tthink I can talkthis one down, man. It's got a mind of its own.
不要跑在我后面  好吗?
Hey, donot run behind me. Okay?
-我们以为它是... -甜心不用道歉
-It's...It's Just that we thought that it was... -Honey, don't apologize.
你们跟我们一起跑
Yeah, you guys are running with us.
哇!  这将是有史以来  最棒的一英里裸奔!
Oh, man!This isgoing tobe the best Naked Mile ever!
晚安...
Good evening...
那是谁?
Who is that guy?
那是人见人怕的诺尔李文斯汀
That isbig, badNoah Levenstein.
这个校园所出过最疯狂的狗杂种
The craziest bastard thiscampus has ever known.
我的错我的错  欢迎参加一英里裸奔
My bad.My bad. welcome to the Naked Mile.
对  我在许久前开始举行这个比赛...
Yes, youknow, when I started this race many, many...
妈的  他在60年代就开始举行这个活动
Christ,he started this whole thing back in the 60's.
当时只是消极的抗议
...manyyears ago. It wasjust... Just a passive protest.
可说只是向当局表达不满而已
Just a way to stick it to the man, so to speak.
好  好
Right on. Right on.
但是多年下来  政治意味变淡了
But overthe years, it'sbecome somewhat less political.
到了现在
And now,it's just
只变成罗马式的性狂欢
some sort of Roman orgy,
我觉得也没什么不好
which I'm down with, by the way.
但是请大家记得
But let's keep one thingin mind.
这是向全世界展现你们的青春活力
This isabout showing theworld your youthfuI exuberance,
以及你们对于高等教育  全心全意的承诺
and yourunabashed commitment to higher learning,
并顺便享乐
and having fun while you're doing it,
裸体的意义也就在于此
which iswhere the nakedpart comes in.
好!
Yeah!
当然  全裸
And being completely naked is, of course,
是非常自然的
a perfectly natural thing.
一个人对于身体各部位
There'snot one part of one's body
都不应感到羞耻
one should be ashamed of,
无论是阴部
be it one's pubicregion
还是
or one'sbreasts,
年轻女孩子  以及一两个
as in the case with you young ladies...
男孩子的乳房  都是一样
...and acouple of you young men.
但是你们都应该为了能展现自我
But youshould all just revel in the glory of being seen
而感到欣喜
as the people youare.
此外  如果任何人有...
Incidentally, ifanyone has anything...
少废话开始吧!
Come on,let's fucking dothis!
我附议年轻人
I secondthat motion, young man.
好  大家准备
Okay, everybody ready.
准备
Get set...
还是硬着吗?
still going?
你知道当然了!
You knowit, baby. Hell,yeah!
你喜欢这一大只吧!
You lovethe BossHogg!
好  看哪看这些咪咪
All right, yeah.Look atthis. Look at all these teats.
我在一群咪咪中  我的G丸拖着地
I'm adrift in a sea of boobies, and my balls are scraping the pavement.
小心
Oh, heads up.
瞧瞧  是这群小男人们
Look, it's the boner guys!
你们的鸟真好看
Nice cocks.
你说的没错
Oh, yougot thatright, sexy.
你的毛病可严重了
Dude, you have serious issues.
嘿  裸体的人才可以!
Hey, naked peopleonly!
-你没事吧?  -没事
-Are Youall right? -I'mfine.
来  甜心我们跑完吧
Come on,sweetie.Let's finish this thing.
我站在终点线  这是个非常荣耀但怪异的传统
I'm standing at the finish line of a very proud, but strange tradition
叫做一英里裸奔
called the NakedMile.
每年在考试过后
Ever year after exams
数百名学生裸体
hundredsof students runa mile through campus
奔跑一英里穿过校园
in nothing more than their birthday suits.
这真是棒极了!
This isthe greatest thing ever!
-耶!  -我们办到了
-Hell, yeah! -Wedid it!
我不敢相信我们做到了!
I can'tbelieve we did this!
对!  一英里裸奔!
Yeah! Naked Mile,baby!
贝塔兄弟会最棒!
Beta House fucking rules!
来吧  马拉松人  准备参加派对吧
Come on,marathonmen. Let's get ready for the party.
我成功了我真的成功了
I did it. I really did it.
加油  表弟  那是我表弟
Way to go, Coz. That's mycousin.
有人说这是猥亵的行为
some people callit lewdbehavior,
但是学生说这只是发泄紧张情绪的好方法
but thestudentssay it'sJust a good way to blow off steam.
也许
And maybe,
也可找到爱情
find love.
这是亥尔麦克斯  在一英里裸奔所做的报导
This isHal Michaels, reporting from the Naked Mile.
史提夫来了!
Stiflerhas arrived!
耶!  耶!
Yeah! Yeah!
妈的!  这真的是同一栋房子吗?
Holy shit! Is this even the same house?
我想我有一个春梦就是这样开始的
I thinkI had a wet dreamthat started like this.
是那些人
It's those guys.
然后那样结束
And ended like that.
哇  吞那些药丸
Wow, taking thosepills
恐怕是你们所做过让自己最受欢迎的一件事
might Just be thebest thing you guys ever did for your social lives.
对
Oh, yeah.
要不要跳舞?
You wanna dance?
这还用说吗?  当然库斯要跳舞
Is my dick hard?Of course the Cooze wants to dance.
你要跳舞吗  性感的?
Are yougonna dance, sexy?
还是你是那种耍酷而不跳舞的足球员?
Or are you one ofthose football players who's too cooI to dance?
他们叫我白影  是有原因的
Oh, baby, they don't callme the White shadow for nothing.
来  可爱的
Come on,cutie.
狗杂种
What a bastard.
我早就叫你收回  那张尽情狂欢的许可证
I told you to call off that stupid guilt-free pass.
抱歉  甜心
I'm so sorry, honey.
我们帮得上忙吗?
Is thereanythingwe cando for you?
不用了我想要独处一下
No, I think I Just want to be alone.
才不呢我们不会让你一个人在这里自怨自艾
No way.We are not leaving you alone so you can beat yourself up.
对  可是是我要他去的  现在我总不能生气
Yeah, but I toldhim to do it. I mean, I can't get mad about it now.
不要这么理性好不好崔西?我们是女孩子耶
Would you quit being so logical, Tracy? We're girls.
男孩应该知道不要信任我们做出理性的决定
Boys should knowbetter than to trust us to be rational.
-这不是我们的天性 -真的不是
-It's not in ournature.-It's really not.
所以  你要去打扮一下
So, youare goingto getdressed.
然后我们去艾力森的派对
Then, we're goingto Allison's party.
-这样你就会忘记艾瑞克  -我不想去
-That will get your mindoff of Erik. -I don't want to.
这里没有你决定的余地  快去换衣服
Well, you don't have a vote in this. Now get dressed.
看看我们的男孩  你想他今晚会破宫吗?
Check out our boy. Thinkhe's going to lose it tonight?
不会  我赌他最后会搞砸  然后到厕所去打枪
Nope. Bet he screws it upand ends up Jerking off in the bathroom.
我赌20块他会跟她嘿咻
I'll bet20 buckssays henails her.
好  跟你赌
Oh, you're on.
嘿  勃起兄弟
Hey, hard-on brothers.
你们知道这里每个人都在谈论你们吗?
Do you guys haveany ideahow much everybody here has been talking about you?
-我有这种感觉  -对!
-I was getting that feeling. -Yeah!
好  听好我有个主意
Okay, listen up,Cause Igot a plan
会让你们永垂不朽
that's gonna makeyou guys legends.
各位先生女士!
Ladies and gentlemen!
请以贝塔屋的掌声欢迎  铁棒 莱恩葛林
Give a big Beta House welcome to Ryan steel RodGrimm
和  常硬麦克库斯曼!
and MikeEverhardCoozeman!
耶  库斯!
Yeah, Cooze!
从今夜起我们举行新型态的
Tonightis the dawning ofa new era
无聊男性竞赛
in meaningless male competition.
世界重量级勃起冠军!
The Heavyweight Hard-On Championship of the World!
在竞赛第一阶段
For thefirst phase of the competition,
将在我们参赛者的老二上挂一个水桶
a bucketwill behung onthe dong of each of our contestants.
那个水桶将装满一壶啤酒
That bucket willbe filled with a pitcher of beer.
最先掉下水桶的人就输
First person to drop thebucket is the loser.
开始老二大竞赛吧!
so let the penisgames begin!
开始倒酒!
Commencethe pouring!
-你喜欢吗?  -喜欢宝贝!
-You like that? -Oh, yeah, baby!
真抱歉
Oh, I amso sorryabout that!
还可以
still good.
下一个单元
Next competition.
丢套环
The ringtoss.
-来吧  女生  -来
-Let's have it, girls. -Come on.
对  套在老二上!
That's right! Onthat penis!
来  就像游艺场一样
Come on,baby, Just likesix Flags.
套错头了!
Wrong head!
套在龟头上
Ring around the cocksy.
你那根还差2.5公分
You needed an extra inchon that one.
你相信吗?
Can youbelieve this?
别让库斯赢
Do not let Coozewin.
下个单元!
Next competition!
我有一个23公分的打击区
I got anine-inchstrikezone, baby.
-你自以为很  -绝对不会漏接!
-You cocky prick. -You can't miss it!
是坏球!
It's a hardball,son!
挥棒  挥棒  挥棒
Hey, boner, boner, boner.
挥棒吧!
Swing, boner!
中外野!
Deep center, baby!
界外球!
Foul ball!
短打
Bunt.
好了  打成平手吧
That isit. We'recallingit a tie.
两位同时登上世界勃起冠军的宝座
Your Co-Hard-on Championsof the World,
铁棒莱恩葛林和
Ryan steel RodGrimm and
常硬麦克库斯曼
Mike EverhardCoozeman!
五十六五十七  五十八  五十九...
Fifty-six, fifty-seven, fifty-eight, fifty-nine...
宝贝  谁才是他妈的冠军?
Who's the fuckingchamp,baby?
男孩真是坏榜样
Boys area bad influence.
你不知道他在做什么跟谁做
I mean,you haveno ideawhat he's doing or who he's doing it with.
尽情狂欢的许可证?太好笑了
This guilt-free pass thing? Completely ridiculous.
结果会变成  你们两个再也无法平等
The bottom line is this.You two will never be on the same level again.
你是处女而他不是处男  这样无法维持下去
You're avirgin and he'snot. It's Just not gonna work.
那要怎么办?  我应该跟他分手吗?
So, what? I'm supposed tobreak up with him?
不  但你必须回到平等的状况
No, butyou needto get back on the same level.
你今晚必须跟一个人嘿咻
You needto sleepwith somebody. Tonight.
-布鲁克 -闭嘴  娜塔莉
-Brooke. -Shut up, Natalle.
只有这样才行  想想看  一个月后
It's theonly way. lmagine a month from now,
你决定跟艾瑞克上床了
you decide to doit withErik.
你会想
All you're goingto be thinking is that
他已经跟另一个女孩上过床
he's already hadsex withsome other girl.
除非你也这样  否则这段感情将无法平等
The relationshipwill notbe equal unless you do this.
看  那是川特
Oh, look. There'sTrent.
好极了
Perfect.
-酷  撞球桌  你会玩吗?  -有时
-Hey, cool. A pooI table.Do you play? -Sometimes.
-想玩什么?  -随便
-Well, what do you want to play? -I don't care.
好  九球好吗?  九球
Okay. Well, how about nine-ball? Look, nine-ball.
很简单
It's...It's easy.
只要按顺序  从一号球打到九号球就好
You Just have toget theballs in order from one through nine.
我来示范我先开球你会打得很好的
I'll show you. I'll breakright now. You'll be good at it.
-艾瑞克 -怎样?
-Erik. -Yeah.
来
Come here.
这对你很特别  对吧?
This isspecial to you, right?
我是说这个周末  今夜?
I mean,this weekend, this night?
-艾瑞克? -怎样?
-Erik? -Yes?
这是性不是莎士比亚
This issex, notshakespeare.
你真的要吗?  因为我恐怕不会很行
Are yousure youwant to?Because I doubt I'll be very good.
别担心我知道如何对待你这样的男孩
Don't worry. I know how to handle guys like you.
-我这样的男孩?  -处男
-Guys like me? -Virgins.
我会善待处男
I can take care of virgins.
你是说我不是你的第一个处男?
You mean, I'm notyour first virgin?
我得向你招认
I have abit of aconfession.
有些女生喜欢金发男有的喜欢肌肉男
some girls like blonds, some like muscles.
我喜欢处男
I like virgins.
你准备好度过特别的一夜吗?
Are youready fora special night?
美人儿我没想到今晚你会来
Hey there, beautiful. Didn't expect to see you here tonight.
我来道歉的  我听说了
I came to apologize. I heard about what happened,
我想要告诉你  我什么都不知道
and I wanted to let you know that I didn't know anything about it.
你不是来整我?
You're not Just here to set me up?
我才不会让这张俊脸受到损伤
I wouldnever want to letanything happen to that gorgeous face.
你确定要在敌人的领土上跳舞?
You sureyou're supposedto be dancing on enemy territory like this?
我想在哪里跳  就在哪里跳
I dancewhere I want,
想跟谁跳就跟谁跳
with whoI want.
我喜欢你的调调
I like your style.
还有你的屁股
And yourass.
你知道我通常不喜欢
You know, I don'tusuallygo for
郊区男孩猛男  和千篇一律的花俏男孩
suburban, Jock, Abercrombie clones,
-不过你很特别  -是吗?
-But there is something about you. -Yeah?
我似乎特别吸引和平者  和吃全素的双性恋人
Well, Itend to have thateffect on pacifist, vegan bisexuals.
这男的品味不错
This guy's got good taste.
你确定在发生了楼下那件事后还想来吗?
You sureyou're up for this after that little incident downstairs?
他们叫我常硬
They don't call me Everhard
可不是因为  我的枪膛里只有一颗子弹
becauseI've only got one bullet in the chamber.
-不过  为了保险起见...  -你还要再吃?
-But Just to be sure... -Should you be taking more of that?
再吃?  我一开始并没有吃
More? Ididn't take it the first time.
-你是说...  -没错宝贝
-You mean... -That's right, baby.
今晚让我们逍遥吧
We're gonna havea good time tonight.
赶快上床你这个没用的乡下人
Now getyour worthless ass on the bed, you peasant.
-你说什么?  -我说上床
-Excuseme? -I said, geton the bed
你这个没用的乡下人!
you worthless peasant!
你怎么搞的?  那是什么?
What isyour problem? Whoa, what's that? What...
-天哪! -我说上床
-Oh, God! -I said, get onthe bed,
这可不是开玩笑
and I meant it.
喔  我知道了
Oh, yeah, baby. Iget it.
我也喜欢
And I'minto it.
闭嘴!
shut up!
好!  好!好!
All right! All right! Allright!
布兰迪
Brandy.
抱歉  我不能  真的很抱歉
Look, Ican't dothis. I'm really sorry, okay?
你很漂亮也很酷
I mean,you're really gorgeous and really cool,
我相信世界上所有男人
and I'msure thatevery single guy on this planet
都很想跟你上床  包括我在内
would love to sleep withyou, including me.
但我就是不行
But I Just can't.
我在恋爱中
I'm in love.
-我希望这个女孩知道她有多幸福  -我非常怀疑
-I hopethis girlknows how lucky she is. -I seriously doubt that.
我要再说一次  这是个很好的惊喜
Got to say it again. It'sa very nice surprise.
-我能说什么?  我也很惊喜 -艾瑞克呢?
-What can I say?I'm fullof them. -So, what about Erik?
我们这周末要尽情狂欢
We're ona weekend guilt-free pass.
-我们要做什么都行 -什么都行?
-we cando anything we want. -Anything?
-什么都行 -听起来很棒
-Anything. -I like the sound of that.
-这是你房间吗?  -是啊  我的小女神
-is Thisyour room? -Why,yes, it is, my diminutive goddess.
好  因为我们会需要
Good, because weare going to need
一点隐私
a littlebit of privacy.
对  你这个可悲的奴隶  继续这样做
That's it, you pathetic slave. Keep doing that.
你不觉得有点过份吗?
Don't you think this is getting a little out of hand?
你还不知道什么叫过份
Oh, youhaven't even seenout of handyet.
我可没要你停止
I didn'tmean wehad to stop.
我们不要停  才刚开始呢
Oh, we're not stopping. We're Just getting started.
准备好来点特别的吗?
You ready to getkinky?
哇靠  这还不够特别?
Whoa, this isn'tkinky yet?
差远了呢
Not evenclose.
那是什么声音?
What isthat noise?
搞什么?
What thehell?
开什么玩笑
You gotto be kidding me.
你要上楼吗?
So, youwanna goupstairs?
要
Yeah, Ido.
史特灵先生  崔西在吗?
Hi, Mr.sterling.Is Tracy home?
哈罗  艾瑞克  他不在
Hello, Erik. No,she's not.
他跟布鲁克和娜塔莉去参加派对了
She's gone to a party with Brooke and Natalle.
喔
Oh.
抱歉打搅了
Okay. Well, sorryto disturb you, then.
晚安!
Have a good night!
臭小子
Crazy little fucker.
我们一定要找到崔西
We gottafind Tracy. We gotta find Tracy.
我们要找到崔西  崔西在哪里?
We gottafind Tracy. Where the fuck is Tracy?
我想性不一定要一对一
I don'tthink sexhas tobe Just one-on-one.
搞什么?
What thehell?
崔西!
Tracy!
嘿!
Hey!
崔西!
Trace!
-你来这里干嘛?  -还骑着马!
-What the hell are you doing here? -And on a horse!
崔西呢?我要找她
Where'sTracy? Ihave tosee her.
我们想你最好离她远一点
We thinkit's best if youJust leave her alone.
什么?  为什么?
What? Why?
因为我们知道  你的姐妹会的那个小骚货
Becausewe know about your little sorority slut.
你们在说什么?
What areyou talking about?
她在电视上看到你亲那个女孩
She sawyou kissthat girl on TV.
妈的  等等  那又怎样?
Shit. Wait a second. so what?
我有尽情狂欢的许可证
I was ona guilt-free pass.
醒醒吧艾瑞克  根本没这种事
Wake up,Erik. There is no such thing.
崔西呢?
Where isTracy?
喔  我们给了崔西一张  尽情狂欢的许可证
Oh, we gave Tracya guilt-free pass,
现在她正在用呢
and she's using it rightnow.
崔西!  崔西!
Tracy! Trace!
嘿  崔西史特灵  你看到她没有?
Hey, hey. Tracy sterling.Have you seen her?
她刚刚跟川特上楼...
I thinkshe wentupstairswith Trent a little...
崔西!
Tracy!
崔西
Tracy.
崔西  你听到我没有?  你在里面吗?
Trace, can you hear me? Are you in there?
崔西  如果你听得到的话  我很抱歉
Trace, if you canhear me, I am sorry.
我对一切都很抱歉
I am really sorryabout everything, okay?
我知道你给我这张许可证  但我没有用它
I know you gave me this pass, but I didn't use it.
我是说我用了  不过只用了几秒钟
I mean Idid useit, butit was only for a few seconds.
我无法继续下去  所以我回来找你  好吧?
I couldn't go through with it, so I came here looking for you, okay?
我不上床也行  真的
Look, Idon't care aboutthe sex. I really don't.
那不是最重要的事最重要的是你
It's notthe mostimportant thing. You are.
崔西  我爱你
Trace, Ilove you.
你听得到吗?  我爱你!
Can youhear me?I love you!
别吵好不好  我们要嘿休了呢
Do you mind? I'mtrying to get laid here.
你为我骑马而来?
You rodea horsefor me?
我听到她的时候  我以为...
When I heard her,I thought...
我也做不下去
I couldn't do it,either.
我也爱你
I love you, too.
我们应该吗?
should we?
我告诉你我的车停在这里
I'm telling you,man. I parked the car right here.
显然你没有  不然它就会在这里
Well, obviously,you didn't, because then it would be right here.
艾瑞克呢?
Where the hell isErik?
我不知道我的内裤在哪里
Dude, Idon't even know where my underwear is.
-有人叫计程车好吗?  -你死到哪里去了?
-Somebody call ataxi? -Where the fuck did you go?
-买早餐 -那好  我饿毙了
-To Getsome breakfast. -Oh, sweet. I'm starving.
-你们昨晚应该很爽吧  -真是完全失控
-I takeit you guys had agood night. -Oh, completely out of hand, bro.
女孩子呢?
Where are the girls?
他们今天早上都走了
They allsplit this morning.
说要到州大参加大派对
Said they had todrive tostate for some big party.
那一定让你觉得很特别
That must make you feel pretty special.
特别?谁在乎特不特别?
special? Who cares about special?
我只知道要爽
All I care aboutis the sex.
我真是爽毙了
And, baby, I hadplenty.Yeah.
你爽到多失控  库斯?
And Justhow outof handwas this sex, Cooze?
我永远不想再提
I don'twanna talk aboutit. Ever.
说到爽你最后跟布兰迪爽到了吗?
speakingof which, did you seal the deal with that Brandy chick?
-没有  -我就说嘛付钱吧
-no. -Itold you.Pay up.
不过我跟崔西爽到了
But I did have sex with Tracy last night.
-你在说什么?  -崔西
-What are you talking about? -Tracy.
我半夜开车回去  车子没油了
I drovehome in the middle of the night, I ran out of gas,
我偷了一匹马  骑到艾力森的派对
stole ahorse, rode overto Allison's party...
-我们在客房做爱 -哇靠  哇靠  哇靠!
-we hadsex in the guestroom. -Whoa, whoa, whoa!
-你偷了一匹马?  -对
-You stole a horse? -Yup.
真的吗?可以骑的马?
A real horse? Like the kind you ride and shit?
-对  真的马  -那太棒了
-Yeah, areal horse. -That's fucking fantastic.
我以为你没这个胆子
I didn'tthink you had the balls for something like that.
-我也是 -你在哪里找到的马?
-Neitherdid I. -Where did you find a horse?
大富市有马吗?
Are there horsesin GreatFalls?
真为你骄傲
Proud ofyou,
史提夫
Stifler.
谢谢你啦不过叫我艾瑞克吧
Thanks,man. I appreciateit. But call me Erik.
-那你觉得如何?  -我这辈子最美好的一夜
-So, howdo you feel? -Best night of my entire life.
明年见大学女生!
See youin a year, college pussy!
收信了
Mail call, bitches.
骑骑
Scooter.
抓抓
Scratchy.
三角架
Tripod.
-什么鬼东西?  -那是什么?
-What the hell? -What isit, man?
我不知道
I don'tknow.
对镜头笑笑吧
Smile for the camera, baby.
真是太烂了
Oh, man.That isfucked up.
史提夫!
Stifler!